## **Marcos Henrique Dogo**

Experience in the IT area a little more than 1 year, performing capture of text using REGEX (Regular Expression) and development of report and component development. Graduated in Systems Analysis and Development course by the UNIFATECIE University Center. I currently work as a self-employed person with deliveries and a driver (UBER).

Custodia Street. 225

Santo Andre, SP, 09240-140

+55 11 93753-2984

marcoshdogo@outlook.com

https://www.linkedin.com/in/marco shdogo-2608/

https://github.com/MarkinhosHD

#### **OBJETIVE**

Trainee in JAVA programming

Trainee Front End

#### **PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE**

# **Grifon Brasil Assessoria Ltda. EPP.** Sao Paulo — *Administrative Assistant.*

MARCH 2016 - JULY 2016

 Working with Text Capture from the Official Gazettes of all over Brazil, using Regular Expression;

### Grifon Brasil Assessoria Ltda. EPP. Sao Paulo — Intern

OCTOBER 2015 - MARCH 2016

Performing Text Capture using Regular Expression;

### **Mahler Tecnologia em Internet LTDA – EPP.** Sao Paulo — *Intern*

SEPTEMBER 2014 - MARCH 2015

- Parameterization of the Gr5 System.
- Report Development.
- Component Development Language used "PostgreSQL".

#### **ACADEMIC BACKGROUND:**

## **UniFatecie University Center** — Analysis and Systems Development

START IN JANUARY 2021 - END IN AUGUST 2023

#### **HARD SKILLS**

### **Back End Training** — *Jdev Treinamentos Online*

JAVA OOP - Beginning on 25/2022 and completed on 26/2022

# **GIT/GITHUB Training** — Dev Superior (YouTube Nelio Alves)

Versioning Basic Course - Complete.

### **SQL Server 2019** — *Alura Ensino Online*

3 training courses - Beginning on 27/2022 in progress.

- SQL SERVER
- MySQL
- RELATIONAL DATABASE MODELING -Conceptual, Logical and Physical

# **Front End by online school** — B7WEB

5 training courses - Beginning on 05/2023 in progress.

- HTML5
- CSS3

#### **PROJECT**

https://portfolio-marcoshdogo.netlify.app/